Muhammad Sherjeel Akhtar

Bachelors Student

Hello, my name is Muhammad Sherjeel Akhtar. I'm currently doing my bachelors in computer science from the National University Of Computer And Emerging Science.

My expertise are Web Development, Intermediate Level Programming, Entry Level

wy experied are vves bevelopment, intermediate bever regramming, bridy bevel

Penetration Testing And WordPress Site Handler And Creation Expert.

Professional History:

2011-09 To Current Graphic Designer At Tribune

- Graphic Designer In A Public Sector Company Tribune
- Manage all the starting to intermediate level Graphics work
- Handle the interface of Web Applications
- Creates The GUI Of Major Mobile Applications

2015-05 To Current Penetration Loop Holes Testing

- Tested API's
- Tested the Entry level loop holes of Websites
- Completed the DOS-sever testings.

2020-12 To Current General Manager At Project X Roleplay

- Moderating the Public
- Deals the general and public issues
- Arrange friendly level spaces

2021-08 To 2022-01 Co-Head Graphic Designing IEEE

- Intermediate level poster creation
- Event banner creation
- Regulating the GUI Team

2021-09 To Current Starting Level Graphic Designer At MLSA

- Entry level Graphics Work
- Contribes in GUI Interface Team

2021-08 To Currrent Video Graphics Member Of ACM

- Video Editor for Events Trailer
- Analyzes the Pre-Made videos and handle the GUI Team

Education:

2004-03 To 2017-06 School Level Education: Cellular Biology

- Studied Biology At Matriculation Level
- Micro Biology And Cellular Analyzation

2018-08 To 2022-08 Higher Education

- Completed the Higher Education In Pr-Engineering
- Specifications In Chemistry And In-Organic Compounds

2020-09 To Current Bachelor Of Computer Science

- Intermediate Level Programming
- Specifying The Suitable Algorithms And Working With Pre-Build Algorithms

Contact

Address

Karachi, 2599

Phone

03024638147

Email

makhtar@gmail.com

Skills

- Web Development* * * * *
- Entry Level DJANGO
- * * * *
- Penetration Testing
- * * *
- WordPress Handler
- ^ ^ ^ ^
- Front-End Designer
- * * * * * *
- Github Profile Expert
- * * * * * *
- Expert Level PS
- * * * * * * *
- Premiere Expert
- * * * *
- React Developer
- * * * * *
- Backend Dev
- * * * * *
- System Admin
- * * * *
- Ruby Expert
- * * *